<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QRH (Old)</string>
    <string name="long_name">Quick Reference Handbook</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="github"><u>github.com/mttrnd/qrh_android</u></string>
    <string name="app_type">Android</string>

    <string name="updated">Updated November 2020</string>
    <string name="about_1">Open-source mobile application adaptation of the Association of Anaesthetists Quick Reference Handbook (QRH) August 2019 version. www.anaesthetists.org/qrh</string>
    <string name="about_2">This material is a derivative of the \"Quick Reference Handbook\" ( www.anaesthetists.org/qrh ) by The Association of Anaesthetists ( www.anaesthetists.org ), used under Creative Commons license CC BY-NC-SA 4.0 ( www.creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0 ).  Subject to Creative Commons license CC BY-NC-SA 4.0. You may distribute original version or adapt for yourself and distribute with acknowledgement of source. You may not use for commercial purposes.</string>
    <string name="about_3">Please report any bugs via the github page</string>
    <string name="about_4">The guidelines in this handbook are not intended to be standards of medical care. The ultimate judgement with regard to a particular clinical procedure or treatment plan must be made by the clinician in the light of the clinical data presented and the diagnostic and treatment options available.</string>
    <string name="CCBYNCSA">Creative Commons License CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</string>

    <string name="splash_1">As this is your first launch, please read and consider all of the following:</string>
    <string name="splash_2a">This application is an open-source adaptation of the Association of Anaesthetists Quick Reference Handbook (QRH); a collection of guidelines for unexpected or uncommon anaesthesia-related emergencies. As per the original accompanying guidance:</string>
    <string name="splash_2b">\"The QRH is not a substitute for learning and practising clinical skills. Nor is it a substitute for being familiar with more detailed guidelines and algorithms, such as those for managing cardiac arrest or difficult airway.\n\nIt\'s essential that clinicians learn about these and practice their implementation elsewhere. For example, it\'s expected that in using the QRH guideline for managing cardiac arrest, clinicians will already have underlying knowledge of conditions causing cardiac arrest and will be competent in providing advanced life support.\n\nThe QRH is also not intended to be used as a rule book every single time one of the guideline situations is encountered. For instance, most ordinary occasions of hypotension will have a simple cause and will respond to obvious remedies. The hypotension guideline becomes useful if the situation is out of the  ordinary or becomes unremitting. Conversely, for the more immediate and uncommon problems, such as cardiac arrest in theatre, the guideline should be used from the outset to help avoid missing out useful steps in resolving the situation.\"</string>
    <string name="splash_3">This application is intended for use only by healthcare professionals in the United Kingdom who are already familiar with the QRH. It is intended to complement and improve access to, but not replace, the original QRH. <b>This application has not been professionally developed nor tested. You must evaluate the application and its content, and exercise your own discretion about its appropriate use.</b> The developer accepts no responsibility for or liability arising from any decision to use in a clinical setting. You should consider the advice of your employer, regulatory and professional bodies regarding the use of software applications, and always exercise professional judgement before relying on information from any source.\n\nThis application is <u>not</u> presented as a medical device in the United Kingdom. <b>It carries no certification markings, regulatory approvals or technical assessment appraisals.</b> According to the latest Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency guidance <i>\"Medical device stand-alone software including apps\"</i> (Last updated 4th June 2020) at the time of this release; software is unlikely to be a device if it just reproduces a paper document in digital format, provides reference information to follow the path of a procedure/treatment, or it has decision points but the healthcare professional decides which path to take (as they ultimately rely on their own knowledge). The developer believes that the application falls within this \'non medical function\' remit.\n\nRegulations may change with time. Distribution by the developer will be ceased if advised to do so or if this application subsequently becomes subject to regulatory approval. Please periodically check whether regulations have changed, and stop using this application if you are unsure about it\'s status. Due to the offline and open-source nature of the application, however, the developer cannot be held responsible for ongoing use and distribution of the application or its source code by other parties beyond such a time.\n\nFor more information please see: https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/medical-devices-software-applications-apps</string>
    <string name="splash_4">"This application reproduces the August 2019 version of the QRH, adapted to fit the mobile application format. Content has largely been transcribed verbatim, except for minor formatting, punctuation and structure tweaks that do not meaningfully alter the guidelines, and the introduction of TALLman Lettering to improve the readability of certain words. The developer assumes no responsibility or liability for any errors or omissions in the content. The information is provided on an \"as is\" basis with no guarantees of completeness, accuracy, usefulness or timeliness. Drug indications and doses may be incorrect, and do not take into account individual circumstances such as comorbidities, interactions, renal and hepatic function. Likewise, the application is provided on an \"as is\" basis with no guarantees of usefulness, performance or reliability. A copy of the original QRH should always be retained for reference and backup. The developer, original QRH authors, or anyone else connected in any way with the QRH or application, cannot be held responsible for your use of the information contained in or linked from this application. Links to external websites and telephone numbers are provided for convenience and informational purposes only; they do not constitute an endorsement and the developer is not responsible for any third-party content accessed through them.\n\nThe QRH is updated from time to time. A version number is displayed next to each guideline in the list view, and in the header and footer when opened; these correspond with the Association of Anaesthetists guideline versioning. You must check that the guidelines you are using are up to date. The developer will endeavour to keep the application updated with any new QRH revision, but there will be a delay between release from the Association of Anaesthetists and release of an application update. If any guidelines contained within the application become superseded, please revert to using the latest version from the Association of Anaesthetists. Alternatively, the source code could be obtained from github.com/mttrnd/qrh_android and updated by the end-user.\n\nThis application does not collect, access, use, store, transmit or sell any personal data. This application does not use any third-party location, advertising or user analytics libraries. Whilst the application itself logs no user information, basic de-identified data may be collected by the Android operating system and/or Google Play unless you have opted-out of provided these; we may access these anonymised statistics to help improve future versions of the application. "</string>
    <string name="splash_5">If you disagree with any of the above, please click the \'EXIT\' button below and uninstall the application. If you agree, please click the \'AGREE &amp; CONTINUE\' button to launch the application. This disclaimer can be accessed at any time from the About page by clicking the icon at the top-right corner of the main application screen. A small popup reminder of this disclaimer and the unofficial nature of this QRH adaptation will be displayed at each launch.</string>
    <string name="splash_6">Thank you for reading</string>

    <string name="arrow">Arrow</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="version_hint">Adapted from QRH section </string>
    <string name="emptySearch">No results</string>

    <string name="locations_header">Locations</string>
    <string name="locations_additional">Additional locations</string>

    <string name="location_arrest">Cardiac arrest trolley</string>
    <string name="location_pacing">Pacing defibrillator</string>
    <string name="location_airway">Airway rescue trolley</string>
    <string name="location_mh">Dantrolene / malignant hyperthermia kit</string>
    <string name="location_la">Lipid rescue / local anaesthetic toxicity kit</string>
    <string name="location_anaphylaxis">Anaphylaxis kit</string>
    <string name="location_rapid">Rapid infusor for i.v. fluid</string>
    <string name="location_salvage">Cell salvage equipment</string>
    <string name="location_ultrasound">Ultrasound machine</string>
    <string name="location_videoscope">Videolaryngoscope</string>
    <string name="location_cric">Cricothyrotomy kit</string>
    <string name="location_jet">Jet ventilator</string>
    <string name="location_scope">Flexible intubating scope</string>
    <string name="location_helpp">Ramping mattress for obese</string>
    <string name="location_muster">Muster points for evacuation</string>
    <string name="location_cooled">Cooled fluids</string>
    <string name="location_ice">Nearest ice machine</string>    <string name="location_sugammadex">Sugammadex</string>
    <string name="location_firealarm">Fire alarm</string>  <string name="location_fireext">Fire extinguisher</string>

    <string name="location_equipmentbox">EQUIPMENT LOCATIONS</string>
    <string name="location_settingshint">Please enter locations (top-right)</string>

    <string name="location_additional_1a">Additional 1 name</string>
    <string name="location_additional_1b">Additional 1 content</string>
    <string name="location_additional_2a">Additional 2 name</string>
    <string name="location_additional_2b">Additional 2 content</string>
    <string name="location_additional_3a">Additional 3 name</string>
    <string name="location_additional_3b">Additional 3 content</string>


    <string name="fire1">Evidence of fire (smoke, heat, odour, flash, flame) on patient or drapes, or in patient’s airway</string>
    <string name="fire2">START</string>
    <string name="fire3">Call for help and inform theatre team</string>
    <string name="fire4">&lt;li&gt;Activate fire alarm&lt;li&gt;Dial hospital fire emergency number and report location and nature of fire&lt;li&gt;Bring CO2 fire extinguisher into theatre</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="agree_amp_continue"><![CDATA[Agree & Continue]]></string>

    <string name="disclaimers">View disclaimers</string>
    <string name="resetexit">Reset data &amp; exit</string>
    <string name="iconhint">Click this icon at the top\-right of each guideline to access the original PDF file from the Association of Anaesthetists website.</string>
    <string name="settinghint">Click this icon at the top\-right of pages 0\-4 and 3\-7 to edit location reminders.</string>
    <string name="arrowhint">Click highlighted links to jump to related guidelines.</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="_4">4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_guideline_list">Guidelines</string>
    <string name="title_guideline_detail">Guideline Detail</string>

</resources>