<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QRH</string>
    <string name="long_name">Quick Reference Handbook</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_download">Download</string>
    <string name="github"><u>github.com/anaes-dev/qrh-android</u></string>
    <string name="app_type">Android</string>

    <string name="updated">Updated December 2020</string>
    <string name="about_1">Unofficial open-source mobile application adaptation of the Association of Anaesthetists Quick Reference Handbook (QRH) August 2019 version. www.anaesthetists.org/qrh</string>
    <string name="about_2">This material is a derivative of the \"Quick Reference Handbook\" ( www.anaesthetists.org/qrh ) by The Association of Anaesthetists ( www.anaesthetists.org ), used under Creative Commons license CC BY-NC-SA 4.0 ( www.creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0 ).  Subject to Creative Commons license CC BY-NC-SA 4.0. You may distribute original version or adapt for yourself and distribute with acknowledgement of source. You may not use for commercial purposes.</string>
    <string name="about_3">Please report any bugs via the github page</string>
    <string name="about_4">The guidelines in this handbook are not intended to be standards of medical care. The ultimate judgement with regard to a particular clinical procedure or treatment plan must be made by the clinician in the light of the clinical data presented and the diagnostic and treatment options available.</string>
    <string name="CCBYNCSA">Creative Commons License CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</string>

    <string name="splash_1">As this is your first launch, please read and consider all of the following:</string>
    <string name="splash_1b">Please check for any changes to the disclaimers with this update:</string>
    <string name="splash_2a">This application is an unofficial open-source adaptation of the Association of Anaesthetists Quick Reference Handbook (QRH); a collection of guidelines for unexpected or uncommon anaesthesia-related emergencies. As per the original accompanying guidance:</string>
    <string name="splash_2b">\"The QRH is not a substitute for learning and practising clinical skills. Nor is it a substitute for being familiar with more detailed guidelines and algorithms, such as those for managing cardiac arrest or difficult airway.\n\nIt\'s essential that clinicians learn about these and practice their implementation elsewhere. For example, it\'s expected that in using the QRH guideline for managing cardiac arrest, clinicians will already have underlying knowledge of conditions causing cardiac arrest and will be competent in providing advanced life support.\n\nThe QRH is also not intended to be used as a rule book every single time one of the guideline situations is encountered. For instance, most ordinary occasions of hypotension will have a simple cause and will respond to obvious remedies. The hypotension guideline becomes useful if the situation is out of the  ordinary or becomes unremitting. Conversely, for the more immediate and uncommon problems, such as cardiac arrest in theatre, the guideline should be used from the outset to help avoid missing out useful steps in resolving the situation.\"</string>
    <string name="splash_3">This application is intended for use only by healthcare professionals in the United Kingdom who are already familiar with the QRH. It is intended to complement and improve access to, but not replace, the original QRH. <b>This application has not been professionally developed nor tested. You must evaluate the application and its content, and exercise your own discretionary judgement about its appropriate use.</b> The developer accepts no responsibility for or liability arising from any decision to use in a clinical setting. You should consider the advice of your employer, regulatory and professional bodies regarding the use of software applications, and always exercise professional judgement before relying on information from any source.\n\nThis application is <u>not</u> presented as a medical device in the United Kingdom. <b>It carries no certification markings, regulatory approvals or technical assessment appraisals.</b> According to the latest Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency guidance <i>\"Medical device stand-alone software including apps\"</i> (4th June 2020) at the time of this release; software is unlikely to be a device if it just reproduces a paper document in digital format, provides reference information to follow the path of a procedure/treatment, or it has decision points but the healthcare professional decides which path to take (as they ultimately rely on their own knowledge).\n\nRegulations may change with time. Distribution by the developer will be ceased if advised to do so or if this application subsequently becomes subject to regulatory approval. Please periodically check whether regulations have changed, and stop using this application if you are unsure about its status. Due to the offline and open-source nature of the application, however, the developer cannot be held responsible for ongoing use and distribution of the application or its source code by other parties beyond such a time.\n\nFor more information please see: https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/medical-devices-software-applications-apps</string>
    <string name="splash_4">This application reproduces the August 2019 version of the QRH, adapted to fit the mobile application format. Content has largely been transcribed verbatim, except for minor formatting, punctuation and structure tweaks that do not meaningfully alter the guidelines, and the introduction of TALLman Lettering to improve the readability of certain words. The developer assumes no responsibility or liability for any errors or omissions in the content. The information is provided on an \"as is\" basis with no guarantees of completeness, accuracy, usefulness or timeliness. Drug indications and doses may be incorrect, and do not take into account individual circumstances such as comorbidities, interactions, renal and hepatic function. Likewise, the application is provided on an \"as is\" basis with no guarantees of usefulness, performance or reliability. A copy of the original QRH should always be retained for reference and backup. The developer, original QRH authors, or anyone else connected in any way with the QRH or application, cannot be held responsible for your use of the information contained in or linked from this application. Links to external websites and telephone numbers are provided for convenience and informational purposes only; they do not constitute an endorsement and the developer is not responsible for any third-party content accessed through them.\n\nThe QRH is updated from time to time. A version number is displayed next to each guideline in the list view, and in the header and footer when opened; these correspond with the Association of Anaesthetists guideline versioning. You must check that the guidelines you are using are up to date. The developer will endeavour to keep the application updated with any new QRH revision, but there will be a delay between release from the Association of Anaesthetists and release of an application update. If any guidelines contained within the application become superseded, please revert to using the latest version from the Association of Anaesthetists. Alternatively, the source code could be obtained from github.com/anaes-dev/qrh-android and updated by the end-user.</string>
    <string name="splash_5">This application does not itself collect, access, use, store, transmit or sell any personal data. Basic de-identified data may be collected by the Android operating system and/or Google Play - as governed by their respective privacy policies - unless you have opted-out of providing these; we may access these anonymised statistics to help improve future versions of the application.</string>
    <string name="splash_6">If you disagree with any of the above, please click the \'EXIT\' button below and uninstall the application. If you agree, please click the \'AGREE &amp; CONTINUE\' button to launch the application. This disclaimer can be accessed at any time from the About page by clicking the icon at the top-right corner of the main application screen. A small popup reminder will be displayed at each launch.</string>
    <string name="splash_7">Thank you for reading</string>

    <string name="arrow">Arrow</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="version_hint">Adapted from QRH section </string>
    <string name="emptySearch">No results</string>

    <string name="snackLaunch">Unofficial adaptation of Quick Reference Handbook\nNot endorsed by the Association of Anaesthetists\nUntested and unregulated; not recommended for clinical use\nNo guarantees of completeness, accuracy or performance\nShould not override your own knowledge and judgement</string>
    <string name="old_android"><b>This app displays best on Android Nougat or later.</b>\n\nYou may continue to use on older Android versions, however certain formatting (particularly bulleted lists) may not display optimally.</string>
    <string name="app_update">Updated to latest version.</string>

    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="agree_amp_continue">Agree &amp; Continue</string>

    <string name="disclaimers">View disclaimers</string>
    <string name="privacy">View privacy policy</string>
    <string name="iconhint">Click this icon at the top\-right of each guideline to access the original PDF file from the Association of Anaesthetists website.</string>
    <string name="arrowhint">Click highlighted links to jump to related guidelines.</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="_4">4</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="label_warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="label_tick">Green tick</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>

    <string name="disable_dark_mode">Disable automatic theme</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="dark_explanation">The app will automatically follow the system setting unless overridden here:</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>